Jiin Choi



→ Affiliation: Biomedical convergence science & technology, School of concergence, Kyungpook National University

→ Address : Daejeon Yuseong-gu expo-ro 448

→ E-MAIL : dim04018@knu.ac.kr

 \rightarrow Phone : 010-7632-1365

→ jiin04018.github.io

CAREER GOAL:

My dream is to become an expert in various Omics data analysis. As genomic sequencing technologies are developing faster than ever, I would contribute to develop about sequencing data analysis technology. Also, I want to help to improve therapeutic methods and diagnostic methods about many incurable diseases by approaching bioinformatics. Recently, I would like to develop innovative AI drug discovery method by applying the aforementioned technologies to deep learning.

RESEARCH INTEREST:

- 1. Cancer genomics
- 2. Bioinformatics
- 3. Precision medicines
- 4. Deep learning

MILITARY SERVICE:

2017.03 ~ 2018.12 : Completed military service at the ROKA

EDUCATION:

B.S:

Department of Bioscience, Biotechnology, Kyungpook National University (2016.03 - 2022.02)

M.S:

Biomedical convergence science & technology, School of convergence, Kyungpook National University (2022.03 - Present)

LANGUAGE EFFICIENCY:

TOEIC: 840

RESEARCH EXPERIENCES:

▶2021.07 ~ 2021.08 : Research Intern at Personalized Genomic Medicine Research Center, Korea Research Institute of Bioscience and Biotechnology(KRIBB), Korea / Summer internship

▶2021.09 ~ 2022.02 : Research intern at Computational Genomics Lab, Department of Biomedical convergence science & technology, Kyungpook National University, Korea / Undergraduate

OTHERS ACTIVITIES:

▶2016.03 ~ 2016.12 : Joining volunteer group in Department of Natural science, Kyungpook National University

- ▶2021.03 ~ 2021.06 : COVID-19 campus preventer at Kyungpook National University
- ightharpoonup 2021.08: Academic Excellence Scholarship , Kyungpook National University
- ▶2021.09 ~ 2021.12 : Taking a online lecture of K-Genome Online Lecture(KGOL) Easy Genome Analysis for Biomedical engineer
- ▶2022.01 ~ 2022.02 : Mentee of 2022 winter job mentoring program, Samsung Bioepis(EPIS Day, J/D : Clinical Project Manager)

Projects:

► Analysis of Various Brain Tumor Transcriptome with Immune Expression and Cell Types

(Sep. 2021 ~ Present)

► Single cell RNA sequencing in Gastric Cancer, Kyungpook
National University Hospital, Korea / Gene expression profiling of
Gastric cancer single cell RNA sequencing data

(Mar. 2022 ~ Present)

CERTIFICATIONS:

Certification of Korean history Level 1
Word processor certification
Computer specialist in spread sheet & Database Level 2
Genetic data analyst level 1 (KGOL)

TOOLS and SKILLS:

Microsoft excel, Python, Pandas, R, Linux, Bash, Basics of tensorflow

DECLARATION:

The information provided above is accurate to the best of my knowledge.